Leonardo Chinem Kameya

Personal Info



First Name: Leonardo Chinem

Last Name: Kameya

Date of Birth: 1989-10-31

Web: www.lkameya.com

Nationality: Brasileira

Address: 496 Palestina St. Vila Palmira, Campo Grande, Brazil

Phone number: +5567992022050

Email address: leonardo.kameya@gmail.com

Profile

I have 6 years of experience as a web developer and through continuous studies on new technologies I try to adapt new projects to the best practices in the agile process of development. I have more experience working with the .NET platform using the C # language, however I am looking for new opportunities and I am available to learn and improve my skills in other languages and platforms as well. I value the final quality of the product delivered to the customer through a dynamic and motivated team that values the continuous improvement and dissemination of knowledge among the team.

Certification: MCPS: Microsoft Certified Professional & MS: Programming in HTML5 with JavaScript and CSS3.

Work experience

Sanesul Developer 2014-07 - present

Campo Grande C#, JavaScript, CSS3, HTML5, React.JS

Brasil Version Control: Git

AZ Informática Systems Analyst 2013-06 – 2014-06

Campo Grande Languages: Natural / C#

Brasil Databases: ADABAS / SQL Server Tools: Balsamiq, Astah, Bizagi Modeler

Itel Informática Systems Technician 2010-04 – 2012-04

Campo Grande Languages: C#, VB.net

Brasil Tools: Visual Studio 2010, SQL Server 2008, Microsoft Office

Education

Campo Grande

Brasil

Universidade Systems Analysis 2007-01 – 2011-11
Federal de Mato Grosso do Sul

Languages